http://www.willmaster.com/privacy-policy.php

Software, your way.
How To Get Good Custom Software
(Download)
(PDF)
Will Bontrager Software LLC Privacy Policy
Will Bontrager Software LLC ("us", "we", or "our") has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy.
The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the websites operated by us (the "Websites").
Links
The Websites contain links to other websites, which may be information, advertising, or other links. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
As remuneration for the time and research involved to provide quality links, we generally use affiliate links when we can. Whenever we link to anywhere other than the Websites, you should assume they are affiliate links or that we benefit in some way.
Information Gathered by Third Parties and Other Websites
Third parties and other websites may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, or logging access or activity, in the course of content pages, ads, or other content being served or responded to at the Websites. We have no authority over, and can not control, how the information is used.
Ads
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Websites. These companies may use information about your visits to the Websites and other sites on the Internet in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click heresee the section below.
Interest based advertising choices and information:
Please follow links of interest to you.
If any links are disabled or broken, use a contact link at this Website
and request up-to-date links.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the Websites.
Google's use of the DoubleClick DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visits to the Websites and other sites on the Internet.
You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by following the directions found when visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Children
The Websites are designed for use by adults. Any children at the Websites must be accompanied by responsible adults and any interaction with the Websites must be performed by adults. The Websites do not knowingly collect personal information from nor dispense information to children under the age of 13.
Data Collection On The Websites
We may use cookies to customize Websites or provide a better user experience.
Any personally identifying information provided by you and stored on the Websites is secured behind password protected barriers. Personally identifying information that is no longer needed for operations at the Websites is generally deleted within a day.
Unless such is clearly within the purpose or intent of the form, no email address provided on our forms is added to any of our subscription or notification lists.
Personally identifying information, including names, email addresses, and birth dates, are never sold, distributed to third parties, or exchanged for value.
We may compile or mine non-personally identifying information collected by the Websites for statistical, demographic, usage, diagnostic, planning, administrative, content creation, site design, software monitoring, and/or other purposes.
Contact
If you wish to unsubscribe, choose to opt-out, or wish to be removed from any Website's subscription or other database records, use the method provided with emails you receive or, failing that, use a contact link at our WillMaster.com Website and provide us with all information we may require to remove you from our records.
If you wish to view information we may have about you as an individual, use a contact link at our WillMaster.com Website and provide us with (1) all information we may require to find you in our records and (2) the means to confirm you are who you say you are.
Questions
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of any of the Websites, or your interactions with any of the Websites, use a contact link at the WillMaster.com Website and provide us with all information we may require to understand your questions or concerns and to respond to you.
Contact | Terms of Use | About Us
© 1998-2001 William and Mari Bontrager
© 2001-2011 Bontrager Connection, LLC
© 2011-2020 Will Bontrager Software LLC
© 1998-2001 William and Mari Bontrager
© 2001-2011 Bontrager Connection, LLC
© 2011-2020 Will Bontrager Software LLC
